MICHAŁ MARUSZEWSKI

Address · GitHub · Phone · Portfolio

michalmaru10@gmail.com · github.com/M1chae1M · 698 907 778 · m1chae1m.github.io/CV

IT specialist. I've been creating web applications in react for 15 months. I did a 3 month internship as a junior backend developer (node.js). Experience in working as a service technician and a junior specialist in the configuration of remote print servers. I currently reside in Lublin and I am interested in working in this location, although I am open to the possibility of remote work.

EXPERIENCE

08.2022 - 12.2022

SERVICE TECHNICIAN AND A JUNIOR SPECIALIST IN THE CONFIGURATION OF REMOTE PRINT SERVERS

Repair and preparation of devices. Remotely instructing the customer how to repair their devices themselves. Configure remote print servers.

06.2023 - 08.2023

JUNIOR BACKEND DEVELOPER

Designing and implementing various functions in Node.js based applications. Responsibility for writing effective and high quality code and ensuring that the application runs smoothly.

EDUCATION

2016 - 2022

SECONDARY EDUCATION, IT TECHNICIAN - ZSEN LUBLIN

2022 - CURRENTLY

COMPUTER SCIENCE STUDIES – WSEI ACADEMY IN LUBLIN

COURSES

2018

OFFICE PACKAGE ECDL B3 (MS WORD)

2018

ECDL B3 (MS OFFICE PACKAGE ECDL B4 (MS EXCEL)

2019

CISCO NETWORKING ACADEMY

2019

ECDL S6 (WEB EDITING MODULE)

2019

OFFICE PACKAGE ECDL S1 (MS ACCESS)

2021

EDITING 3D PROJECTS AND PRINTING THEM ON 3D PRINTERS

2022

COURSE OF THE RADIO SMART HOME SYSTEM

2022

CONFIGURATION OF REMOTE PRINT SERVERS (SAFE Q)

2022

CONFIGURATION OF REMOTE PRINT SERVERS (OPTIMIDOC)

SKILLS

- Node.js
- React
- Git

- MySQL
- Next.js

SOFT SKILLS

- Ability to work under time pressure
- Communicative
- Ability to acquire knowledge quickly
- I am good at working in a group
- Expanding professional competences in free time
- Ability to work under stress

ACTIVITIES

In my free time after work and preparations for studies, I train powerlifting and strongman.